A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Series 1 FA1029
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Series 1
1955-1991
1960-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA1029
22.27 Cubic Feet 17 record storage cartons.
17 standard record storage cartons.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 25 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Includes, but not necessarily limited to, files regarding course and seminar announcements and evaluations, Academic Committee records, budgets, faculty reports, lectures, student lectures, examinations, lab demonstrations, convocations, fellowships, scholarships and aid, summer programs, requisitions, expenses and surveys.
Other Finding Aids
For Dean of Graduate Studies records that are currently open for scholarly reseach see:
FA224 Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Publications, Series 2.
FA831 Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Convocation Programs, Series 4.
FA832 Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Frank Brink, Jr., Series 6.
Arrangement
Loosely chronological.
- Graduate Students and Advisors, 1958-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Thesis File, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Prospective Graduates, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Faculty Advisors, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Laboratory, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual Reports, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Orientation, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Orientation papers, 1962-1963, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
- Thesis and Final Examinatons, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Guide for Graduate Thesis, 1963 November (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Prospective Graduates, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Guide for Graduate Thesis, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Orientation papers, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Prospective Graduates, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Orientation papers, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Prospective Graduates, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Guide for Doctoral Dissertation, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Prospective Graduates, 1967-1968, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
- Guide to Doctoral Thesis, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Prospective Graduates, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Term paper, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Prospective Graduates, 1970-1971, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
- Graduate Research Archives, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Prospective Graduates, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Thesis Titles of all Fellows, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Prospective Graduates, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Graduate Directory, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Guide for Preparation of Thesis, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Institute of International Education, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- IIE Census of Foreign Students, 1956-1976 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Faculty, 1962-1965, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34-36)
- Laboratory Development Grant, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Finances - American Council of Education Survey, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Finances - Social Science Research, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Finances - Peterson's Guide, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Finances - Peterson's Guide and Questionnaires, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Finances - National Science Foundation Graduate Trainee Program, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Publications, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Architecture - Dean's Office, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Stipends, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Student's Travel Reimbursement, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Finances, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Stipends and Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Stipends, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Stipends, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Finances, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Finances, 1970-1971, 1971-1972, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 54-56)
- Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Students on Leave, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Changes in Student Status, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- New York State Higher Education Services Corporation (Box 1, Folder 60)
- State Education Department, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Graduate Fellows, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 62-64)
- Immunochemistry, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- History of Science Seminars, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- History of French Science, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Golgi Apparatus Seminar, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Genetics Seminar, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- General Theory of Relativity, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- General Organic Chemistry, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- General Physiology, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Evolution and Population Genetics, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Elementary Electronics, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Electronic Circuits for Electric Measurement, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Drawing and Watercolor, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Digital Computers, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Differentiation and Development, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Development Biology, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Contemporary Science Seminar, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Combinatorial Aspects of Algebra, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Chemistry of Natural Products, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Cell Biology, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Biosynthetic Mechanisms, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Biophysical Mechanisms, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Biology Seminar, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Biological Basis of Motivation, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Bioenergetics, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Biochemistry of Carbohydrates, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Biochemistry, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Animal Behavior Seminar, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Advanced Calculus, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Student Journal Club, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Organic Chemistry Discussion Group, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Neurophysiology Discussion Group, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Natural History Seminar, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Molecular Biology Discussion Group, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- General Mathematics Colloquium, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Developmental Biology Group, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Behavioral Science Discussion Group, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Arthropod Biology Seminar, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Zootechnics, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Tutorial on Comparative Neuroanatomy, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Topic Seminars in Virology, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Statistical Methods and Design, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Seminar on Communicaton Dances of Bees, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Stationary Gaussian Process, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Topics Related to Oncogenic Mechanisms, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Chemical Reaction Kinetics, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Theories of Reaction Rates, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Advanced Biochemistry Sequence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Lipid Biochemistry - Dr. L. B. Spector, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Biosynthetic Mechanisms - Dr. W. Stoffel, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Animal Virology - Tamm and Choppin, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Application of Electronic Circuits, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Analysis of Digital Computers, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Ancient Egyptian Hieroglyphics, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Biochemistry - Dr. J. Gregory, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Biochemistry Seminar - Dr. Spector, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Biology Seminar - B. Voeller, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Chemistry of Natural Products - Dr. W. Agosta, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Communications and Psycholinguistics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Comparative Invertebrate Physiology, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Comparative Pathology Seminar, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Development of Nervous System, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Elements of Mathematical Physics - Kac, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Endocrinology, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Evolutionary and Population Genetics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- French Scientific Literature - Dr. A. Rothen, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- General Physiology - Dr. M. Rizack, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Genetic Coding and Protein Synthesis, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- History of French Science - Dr. A. Rothen, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Human and Population Genetics, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Immunochemistry - Dr. C. Williams, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Seminars in Immunology, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Introduction to Advanced Calculus and Probability, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Introduction to Stochastic Processes, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Isolation of Enzymes in Crystalline Form, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Methods of Mathematical Physics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Nature of Mathematical Models in Genetics, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Neurobiology - Dr. B. McEwen, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Neurophysiology - Dr. V. Wilson, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- NMR Spectroscopy - Dr. Gibbons, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Organic Characterization and Synthesis, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Optical Rotary Dispersion and Circular Dichroism, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Seminar in Contemporary Science, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Particle Physics - Drs. Pagel and Pais, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Philosophy, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Photochemistry and Photobiology - Dr. Mauzerall, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Private Biology Seminar, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Thermodynamics and Statistical Mechanics, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Russian - Mrs. H. Solow, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Scientific Writing - Dr. F. P. Woodford, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Selected Topics in Quantum Mechanics, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Topics in Theory of Solutions - Dr. G. Manning, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Theory of Structure and Confirmation of Macromolecules, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Application of Scattering Theory to Chemical Kinetics, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Atomic Structure and Quantum Mechanics, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Bioenergetics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Biosynthetic Mechanisms, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Chemistry of Natural Products, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Computer Programming, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Seminar on the Concept of Rule-Like Behavior, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- The Cytology of Secretion and its Significance, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Elementary Electronics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Genetics Seminar, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- German - Dr. Karlin, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Immunity to Parasites, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Immunology Seminars, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Introduction to Advanced Calculus, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Introduction to Set Theory, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Ionic Solutions, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Macromolecules, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Mathematical Methods of Physics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Mitochondrial Structure and Function, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Molecular Spectroscopy and Structure, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Nucleic Acids, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Optical Rotary Dispersion and Circular Dichroism, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Physical Chemistry and Macromolecules, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Physiological Experimental Psychology, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Plant Physiology Seminar, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Probability, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Radiation and its Interaction with Matter, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Russian, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Scientific Communication, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Seminar in Communication and Psycholinguistics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Seminars in Contemporary Science, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Seminar on Evolution and Population Genetics, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Seminar on Developmental Biochemistry, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Scientific Communication, I, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Some Problems in Enzyme Specificity, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Statistics, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Structure and Dynamics of Genetic Material, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Vision and the Retina, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Virology Seminar, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Tumor Transplantation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- The Stucture and Replication of the Bacterial Cell and its Macromolecular Components, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Miscellaneous Seminars, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Viruses and Cell Membranes - Dr. P. Choppin, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Virology Course - Drs. Choppin and Tamm, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Tutorial in Organic Chemistry - Dr. Agosta, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Topics in Scientific Communication - Dr. Woodford, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Set Theory Seminar - Dr. R. B. Jensen, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Selected Topics in Quantum Mechanics - Dr. Beg, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Seminars on Mechanisms of Gene Regulation and the Evolution of the Genome, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Seminar on Human Intellectual Development, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Seminar on Evolution and Population Genetics, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Seminar on Abnormal Psychology - Mr. Azmitia, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Seminars in Human Biology, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Seminars in Contemporary Science, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Seminar Course in Animal Behavior - Drs. Griffin, Marler, Nottenbohm, Payne, and Penney, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Russian - Mrs. Cosman, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Recursive Functionals of Higher Type - Dr. J. R. Schoenfield, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Principles of Thermodynamics and Statistical Mechanics - G. E. Uhlenbeck, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Principles of the Structure and the Conformation of Macromolecules - Dr. Nemethy, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Population Genetics and Evolution - Dobzhansky, Ayala, Ehrman, Richmond, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Physical Chemisty of Polyelectrolytes - Dr. R. M. Fuoss, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Physical Chemistry of Macromolecules - Drs. G. M. Edelman, Gall, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Physical Chemistry Course and Tutorial - Drs. Mauserall and Manning, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Physical Biochemistry Journal Club - Drs. Printz and Nemethy, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Optical Rotary Dispersion and Circular Dichroism - Dr. Perlmann, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Neurophysiology - Dr. V. Wilson, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Modern Inorganic Chemistry - Drs. H. B. Gray, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Mathematics Survey and Methods of Mathematical Physics - M. Schreiber, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Mathematical Physics - Dr. K. M. Chase, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Magnetic Resonance in Chemistry and Biology - Dr. Gibbons, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Lysogeny - Dr. Walter Doerfield, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- Lectures in Art, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Joint Seminar on Probability and Related Topics - Rockefeller and Courant Institute, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Instruction to Probability Theory - Drs. Kac and Pitt, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- Introduction to Logic - Dr. Tharp, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- History of French Science - Dr. A. Rothen, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Grammatical Theory - Dr. Paul Postal, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- German - Mrs. Berliner-Kollisch (Box 2, Folder 126)
- General Physiology - Dr. M. Rizack, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Field Course in Animal Behavior, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Environmental Science Lectures - Riker, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Elementary Number Theory - Schreiber, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Elementary Electronics - Eisenberg, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Digital Techniques - Silverman, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- Developmental Biology Discussion Group - Gordon, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Comparative Pathology - Dr. Leader, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Comparative and Functional Neuroanatomy - Dr. Meikle, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Cell Fractionation Technigues - Berthet, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 136)
- Calculus and Analytic Geometry - Pittenger, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Biosynthetic Mechanisms - Spector, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Biophysical Mechanisms Related to Membrane Transport Phenomena, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Biology Seminar, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Biochemistry Seminar - Walsh, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Biochemistry of Polysaccharides, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Ax-Kochen Theory - Shoenfield, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Aspects of Comparative Invertebrate Physiology, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- Anthropod Biology Seminar - R. Richmond, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Animal Behavior Discussion Group - Green and Miissakian, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 146)
- Ancient Egyptian Hieroglyphics - Goudsmit (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Theoretical Inorganic Chemistry, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Techniques Used in Nucleic Acid Research, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 149)
- Statistical Theory of Neutron Capture Levels, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- Special Course in Cell Biology, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- Ontology of Behavior, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 152)
- Structure and Enzymatic Activity of Proteins, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- Structure and Conformation of Macromolecules, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Human and Medical Genetics, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 155)
- Quantum Field Theory - Dr. Khuri, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 156)
- Physical Chemistry of Electrolytes, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 157)
- Physical Chemistry Tutorial, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 158)
- Physical Biochemistry Journal Club, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 159)
- Photobiology - Dr. Mauzerall, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 160)
- Orientation Course in Life Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 161)
- Numerical Methods and Fortran Programming, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 162)
- Neurophysiology Seminar, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 163)
- Motivation and Learning Course - Dr. Pfaffmann, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 164)
- Molecular Structure and Spectroscopy - W. Gibbons, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 165)
- Miscellaneous Seminars, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 166)
- Mathematics Courses - Dr. Schreiber, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 167)
- Mathematical Logic - Dr. Krbacek, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 168)
- Lipid Chemistry - W. Stoffel, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 169)
- High Energy Physics - Dr. A. Pais, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 170)
- General Physiology - Dr. Rizack, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 171)
- Elementary Electronics - Dr. Eisenberg, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 172)
- Cell Biology Seminar Series, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Cell Biology Seminar - Dr. G. Whaley, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 174)
- Biophysical Mechanisms Underlying Transport in Physiological Membranes, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 175)
- Bioenergetics - Dr. deDuve, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 176)
- Biochemstry of Polysaccharides, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 177)
- Biochemstry of Plant Viruses: Dr. Reddi, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 178)
- Behavioral Sciences Seminar, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 179)
- Axiom of Determinateness - Dr. Martin, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 180)
- Applications of Group Theory to Problems in Physics, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 181)
- Ancient Egyptian Hieroglyphics - Dr. Goudsmit, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 182)
- Virology - Dr. Tamm, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 183)
- Structure and Function of Biologically Important Macromolecules, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 184)
- Thermodynamics and Statistical Mechanics, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 185)
- Radioisotope Handling and Use - Dr. Printz, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 186)
- Quantum Mechanics - Dr. Case, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 187)
- Protein Chemistry (Conformational Analysis), 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 188)
- General Physiology - Dr. Rizack, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 189)
- Statistical Physics Seminar, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 190)
- Physical Chemistry - Dr. Mauzerall, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 191)
- Physical Chemistry - Dr. Fouss, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 192)
- Analytical and Physical Chemistry of Peptides and Proteins, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 193)
- Parasitism and Symbiosis - Dr. Trager, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 194)
- Student Orientation Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 195)
- Number Theory - M. Schreiber, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 196)
- Neurophysiology - Dr. V. Wilson, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 197)
- Neurobiology and Behaviour - Dr. Grafstein, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 198)
- Chemistry of Natural Products - Dr. W. Agosta, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 199)
- Motivation and Memory, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 200)
- Molecular Biology of Nucleic Acids, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 201)
- Miscellaneous Seminars, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 202)
- Logic and Model Theory Seminar, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 203)
- Fortran Programming, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 204)
- Environmental Biology - Hutchinson, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 205)
- Cell Hybridization Study Group - Gordon, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 206)
- Brain Mechanism of Behavior - Dr. Pfaff, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 207)
- Bioenergetics - Dr. deDuve, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 208)
- Theoretical Inorganic Biochemistry, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 209)
- Biochemistry of Polysaccharides, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 210)
- Biochemistry Seminar, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 211)
- General Biochemistry, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 212)
- History and Philosophy of 19th Century Biology, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 213)
- Behavioral Sciences Seminar, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 214)
- Behavioral Sciences Seminars Faculty, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 215)
- Behavior-Ecology Seminars, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 216)
- Physiological Aspects of Animal Behavior, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 217)
- Cornell - RU - Course Announcements (Box 2, Folder 218)
- Vision, Retina, Brain, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 219)
- Statistical Methods in Science - Dr. Kac, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 220)
- Spectroscopy Laboratory - Gibbons, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 221)
- Seminars in Reproductive Biology, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 222)
- Physiological Basis of Reinforcement, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 223)
- Physical Chemisty Tutorial, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 224)
- Physical Chemistry, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 225)
- Photochemistry and Photobiology - Dr. Mauzerall, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 226)
- Parasitism and Symbiosis - Dr. Trager, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 227)
- Neuroanatomy Practicum - Dr. Leonard, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 228)
- Miscellaneous Seminars, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 229)
- Math-Physics Colloquium, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 230)
- Mathematics Tutorials - Dr. Kac, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 231)
- Right Logic for the Finite Mind - Dr. Tharp, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 232)
- Intrinsic Characterization of Logic - Tharp, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 233)
- Fortran IV - Dr. Schoenfield, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 234)
- Environmental Science Seminars, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 235)
- Discussion Group for Faculty - Silverstein, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 236)
- Chemical Communications - Griffin, O'Connell, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 237)
- Cell Biology - Dr. Luck, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 238)
- Biologically Important Macromolecules, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 239)
- Bioenergetics - Dr. deDuve, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 240)
- General Biochemistry - Dr. Gregory, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 241)
- Behavioral Science Seminar, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 242)
- Animal Behavior - Field Course, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 243)
- Psycholinguistics - Jarvella, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 244)
- Probability Theory, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 245)
- General Physiology, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 246)
- Physiochemical Foundations of Molecular Biology, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 247)
- Physical Chemistry (Box 2, Folder 248)
- Photochemistry and Photobiology, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 249)
- Philosophy, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 250)
- Organic Chemistry (Advanced), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 251)
- Ontology of Behavior, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 252)
- Neurobiology - Cornell, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 253)
- Membrane Biophysics - Mauro, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 254)
- Mathematics - Schreiber, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 255)
- Learning and Memory - Pfaffmann, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 256)
- Immunology - Krause, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 257)
- Fortran, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 258)
- Conformational Analysis - Perlmann, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 259)
- Comparative and Functional Neuroanatomy - Pfaffmann, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 260)
- Chemical Synthesis of Peptides and Proteins, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 261)